Marah Nakad Architect

Summary Statement

Enthusiastic architect, embraces challenges and innovations in the field of designing and implementing buildings and urban projects with three years of experience working, participated in designing several diverse projects.

High skills in using drawing and engineering design programs, as well as using presentation and presentation programs, ability to communicate effectively with clients and other engineers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Architecture engineer at Modern design office Syria - Swaida 2022 - 2024

- Convert the design or implementation drawings into shop drawings, by adding the details, dimensions, labels, symbols and notes necessary to clarify how to manufacture, install and assemble required elements.
- Design the installation details on the stone facades, which is the method by which the stones are connected to the structural frame using Revit.

Interior designer

Freelancer

2021 - 2022

- For Emirates, Kuwait, Turkey, Egypt, Libya and finally America at PNE Building Company.
- Providing effective interior designs for the commercial and residential markets.
- Commitment to the client's preferences and provide advice when needed.
- Project delivery on time.

Graphic designer Glitch group 2021 - 2022

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Architecture Damascus University 2016 - 2021

presented a project entitled reorganization the Hal Market Area in Swaida that presented the best possible solutions to the region and it received a score of 83.

participated in many activities during my university studies and obtained certificates in them.

Skills

- Creative visualization.
- Blueprint interpretation.
- Proficiency in engineering.
- design programs.
- Time management.
- Research and development.
- CAD drafting.
- Adaptable.
- Problem-Solver.
- Continuous improvement.
- Communication.
- Detail-oriented.



Phone: +936936108514 Address: Syria, Swaida

Email: marah.nakad.1998@gmail.com

Birthdate: June 26th-1998

Nationality: Syrian

LANGUAGES

- Arabic Mother tongue.
- English.

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Autodesk Programs (Autocad, Revit,
- 3Ds Max).
- Adobe Programs (Photoshop, Illustrator, Lumion, V.ray).
- Microsoft .